streamfare.com 2019-01-27

# Privacy Policy

**Our Privacy Policy**  
   
This privacy policy only applies to Streamfare.com located at [http://streamfare.com](http://streamfare.com/). Streamfare.com does **not** collect personally identifying information about individuals except when specifically and knowingly provided by such individuals, which can occur in a variety of contexts such as emails sent to us or through social media comments. This information might be used in order to respond to you when you have a question. You are in complete control of what personally identifiable information you give us.

This web site contains links to external web sites such as those provided by Google through their advertisements. ([Google's policies on information provided by their Ads on this website](https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites)). Note: Advertisements shown to visitors from EU member countries are not personalized ads.

 **Advertiser's cookies** : These cookies collect several pieces of information about your browsing habits. They are usually placed by advertising networks such as Google or Doubleclick. They remember that you have visited this Site and share this information with other organizations, such as advertisers. They do this in order to provide you with targeted advertisements that are more relevant to you and your interests. Although these cookies can track your visits to sites on the Internet, the cookies themselves do not usually know who you are. Without these cookies, online advertisements that you encounter will be less relevant to you and your interests. 

By using this Site, you agree that advertising networks place these types of cookies on your device. If you want more information or if you wish to turn off/on the use of cookies set by individual advertising companies please visit one of the following websites: www.youronlinechoises.com or www.networkadvertising.org/choices. If you would like to take control of only Google/Doubleclick Ads this may be done at the [Google settings page](https://www.google.com/settings/ads/). 

Streamfare uses **Google Analytics** data to better control the content provided to users and uses data provided by Analytics to better serve its content to users. This data is generalized by geo location and device type. No personal data is collected at anytime

Streamfare.com has signed a Data Processing Amendment in order to comply to European privacy laws. Google Analytics provides an opt out tool to provide website visitors more choice on how their data is collected. The add-on communicates with the Google Analytics JavaScript (ga.js) to indicate that information about the website visit should not be sent to Google Analytics.

If you want to opt-out, Google Analytics has an "Opt-out" browser add-on available. You can download and install the add-on for your current web browser. The Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on is available for Microsoft Internet Explorer, Google Chrome, Mozilla Firefox, Apple Safari and Opera. You can get the Google Analytics Opt out Browser Add-on  [HERE](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en)

 **Social Media**  
Third Parties like Facebook, Twitter, Reddit and Google+ are able to place cookies on your device through the use of their social buttons which are included on this website.

Please note that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of other web sites you may visit when you leave Streamfare.com. We recommend that you check the privacy policy of any other web sites you may visit through the web site. The inclusion of links to such web sites does not imply any endorsement of the material on such sites nor any association with their owners or operators. If you have any complaints relating to such sites, please contact them directly.

 **Cookies**  
This Site uses cookies. Cookies are small pieces of text that are written to your hard drive to store information about your use of the Streamfare Website. All Internet browsers  are  probably originally set up to accept cookies, but you can always reset it to refuse them or to ask you each time a site tries to put one on your computer. Please note, if you don’t let  our cookie on your computer, you can still use the Site, but some parts of it might not work correctly. Cookies are a universal function of the internet and the websites which are on it. More detailed information on Cookies at <http://www.allaboutcookies.org/>

If any part of the Streamfare Website links you to other websites, those external websites do not operate under this Privacy Policy. We recommend that you examine the privacy statements posted on those other websites to understand their procedures for collecting, using, and disclosing personal information.

Streamfare may change or modify this Privacy Policy in the future. We will note the date that revisions were last made to this Privacy Policy at the bottom of this page, and any revisions will take effect upon posting. We will notify our members of material changes to this Privacy Policy by either sending a notice to the email address you provided to us or by placing a notice on our Website. We encourage you to check this Privacy Policy from time to time to review the most current version.

Latest revision 05/29/2018

For any further information please email us at: [support@streamfare.com  
](mailto:support@streamfare.com)

Wednesday, February 19, 2020

**HOW TO DISABLE COOKIES  
**  
Here's how to prevent new cookies from being installed and how to delete existing cookies. The exact procedure depends on which browser you are using.  
__________________________Google Chrome  
To prevent new cookies from being installed and delete existing cookies:

<https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?hl=en>

_________________________

 **Firefox**  
To prevent new cookies from being installed:

<https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/enable-and-disable-cookies-website-preferences>

To delete existing cookies:

<https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/delete-cookies-remove-info-websites-stored>

_________________________

 **Internet Explorer**  
To prevent new cookies from being installed and delete existing cookies:

<http://windows.microsoft.com/en-GB/internet-explorer/delete-manage-cookies>

_________________________

 **Safari**  
To prevent new cookies from being installed and delete existing cookies:

<http://help.apple.com/safari/mac/8.0/#/sfri11471>

__________________________

**CHROME HOW TO:** **Allow or block cookies  
for a specific site  
**  
If you allow cookies by default, you can still block them for a certain site.

On your computer, open Chrome.  
At the top right, click the three dots and then Settings. 

At the bottom, click Advanced.  
Under "Privacy and security," click Content settings. Click Cookies.

Next to "Block," "Clear on exit," or "Allow," click Add.

Enter the web address.

To create an exception for an entire domain, insert [*.] before the domain name. For example, [*.]google.com will match drive.google.com and calendar.google.com.

You can also put an IP address or a web address that doesn't start with http://.  
Click Add.

To remove an exception you don't want any more, to the right of the website, click More More and then Remove.
